bookish.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Bookish.com

The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is February 1, 2013.

Following the Terms of Use of Bookish, you will find the Terms of Use of Exquiro, Inc., the online retailer providing the shopping cart on Bookish.

This Privacy Policy applies to the Bookish LLC web site available at [Bookish.com](http://www.bookish.com/), which is operated by Bookish LLC ("BOOKISH," "we," "us" or "our"), and other interactive features, downloads, applications and widgets available through the site that link to this Privacy Policy regardless of whether accessed via computer, mobile device or otherwise (collectively, " **Site** "). This Privacy Policy explains our information collection practices at the Site, such as the types of information we collect regarding visitors to the Site and how we may use that information. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review the Site's [Terms of Use](http://www.bookish.com/terms-of-use), which governs your use of the Site.

 **Information collected from visitors from outside the United States:** If you are visiting the Site from outside the United States and provide us with personal information, please note that your personal information will be transferred, stored and processed within the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By doing business or interacting with us, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to facilities located in the United States and other facility locations selected by us.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [support@bookish.com](mailto:support@bookish.com). If you do not agree with any of the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

### Table of Contents

#### 1\. THE INFORMATION THE SITE COLLECTS AND HOW BOOKISH USES THAT INFORMATION

  * Information You Provide To The Site
  * Public Areas and Information in Your Public Profile
  * Information Provided By Another Web Site
  * Information You Provide About A Third-Party
  * Information Third-Parties Provide About You
  * Information We Collect As You Access and Use The Site

#### 2\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

  * When You Post Information to a Third-Party Web Site or Interact with Third-Party Widgets
  * When You Agree To Receive Information From Third-Parties
  * Third-Parties Providing Services on our Behalf
  * Contests and Promotions
  * Administrative and Legal Reasons
  * Business Transfers

#### 3\. YOUR CHOICES

#### 4\. THIRD-PARTY CONTENT, LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES AND WIDGETS

#### 5\. ONLINE SHOPPING

#### 6\. SECURITY

#### 7\. CHILDREN

#### 8\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

#### 9\. CONTACT INFORMATION

#### 1\. THE INFORMATION THE SITE COLLECTS AND HOW BOOKISH USES THAT INFORMATION

**(a) Information You Provide To The Site**   
This Site is operated in the United States and is designed and targeted to U.S. audiences and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the United States. The Site may ask you to provide personally identifiable information, which is information that could be used to contact you or identify you personally, such as your name, birth date, mailing address, email address or phone number ( **“Personal Information”** ) and other information about you, such as demographic information (your, gender, postal code or similar information) or certain information about your reading habits, preferences and interests. The Site may collect Personal Information and other information about you at various places and forms on the Site, including registration forms, your personal profile page, when you submit a question to us, or when you otherwise communicate or interact with us. If we combine demographic or similar information with the Personal Information we collect, we will treat it as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. 

We may use any information we collect through the Site including your Personal Information: (1) to allow you to participate in the Public Areas (defined below) and other features of the Site; (2) to provide you with information or services that you have requested or agreed to receive; (3) to process your registration with the Site including verifying that your email address is active and valid; (4) to improve the Site or our services; (5) to contact you with regard to your use of the Site and, in our discretion, changes to the Site policies; (6) to ship you a prize from a Promotion (defined below) that may be offered in connection with the Site; (7) for our internal business purposes; and (8) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your Personal Information or with your consent. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of emails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies, and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt-out of receiving such notices from us by following the unsubscribe link in the email from us. Please note that information submitted to the Site via a "contact us" or other similar function may not receive a response. We will not use the information provided by you at the “contact us” function to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your request. 

**(b) Public Areas and Information in Your Public Profile**  
If you register to join the Site ( **"Member"** ), you create a public profile that includes information such as your photo, username, city/state, bio (including activity on the Site) and interests (if you choose to provide them) as well as other information that you choose to post publicly ( **“Profile”** ). Your Profile does not include your date of birth or the number and street portion of your mailing address. The Site may publicly post information about your activity on the Site as a Member, including, without limitation, information about when you last logged into the Site; when you joined the Site; links to web pages you provide; RSS feeds you choose to post; which books you are currently reading; when you updated your Profile; and a list of your book reviews, discussion posts, blog posts and "favorites" (including links to each of those items). Your Profile is publicly viewable by anyone, including all visitors of the Site, unless you go to the Settings section of the Site and select Private for Books or Profile. 

The Site may contain public areas to which you can contribute your original text and other content including, without limitation, a Books section (which includes book ratings and comments); Message Boards section (which includes a variety of different online discussions); and your Profile (collectively, **"Public Areas"** ). If you submit book reviews, book ratings, book comments, blog posts, votes, forum messages, tags (your description of particular content), suggestions, photographs, text, videos or other content to Public Areas ("User Content"), it may be published online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed). Other members of the Site will have access to your User Content and may have the ability to share it with third-parties across the Internet. 

BOOKISH may use your User Content, or any portion of it, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For the full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit to the Site, please review the Site's [Terms of Use](http://bookish.com/terms-of-use). Please note that BOOKISH cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Therefore, do not include Personal Information in your Profile, User Content, a Public Area or any message that you send using the Site that you do not wish to make public. Do not use the Site to arrange a meeting with another member whom you’ve only met online. See the [Terms of Use](http://bookish.com/terms-of-use) for more information about appropriate uses of and content for the Site.

**(c) Information Provided by Another Web Site**  
The Site has functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between your account on the Site and your account on a third-party web site, such as Facebook or Twitter. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party web site providing certain information, including Personal Information, to the Site. For example, when you register with the Site, you may choose to use your Facebook, Twitter, or other supported account from a third-party site to facilitate the registration and login process on the Site. If you choose to use this functionality, the third-party site may send personal information about you to the Site, and the Site may send some or all of your Personal Information to the third-party web site. **If you stop using the Site for any reason or you stop using the third-party platform that you linked to the Site, some or all of your Personal Information may be retained by, and may appear on, the Site or by and on the third-party’s site.**

**(d) Information You Provide About A Third-Party**  
If you send someone else a communication from the Site, such as sending information about a book to a friend, the information you provide (names, email addresses, etc.) is used on a one-time basis to facilitate the communication, and is not saved nor used by us for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly state otherwise. Please ensure that each person to whom you send an email from the Site is someone that you know personally and that you believe is not opposed to receiving the message.

**(e) Information Third-Parties Provide About You**  
We also may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect with information about you from affiliates or third-parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with information we collect through the Site. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any Personal Information received, unless otherwise specifically disclosed by us at the time you provide your Personal Information. 

**(f) Information We Collect As You Access And Use The Site**  
In addition to any Personal Information or other information collected by the Site, our third-party service providers and we may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect certain web site usage information whenever you visit or interact with the Site ( **"Site Usage Information"** ). Site Usage Information may include browser type, operating system, the page served, the time, and the preceding page view, among other information. We may use Site Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including enhancing or otherwise improving the Site. In addition, your IP address or some other unique identifier for the particular device you use to access the Site (a **"Device Identifier"** ), as applicable, may be collected. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer, your mobile phone, or other device (any, a **"Device"** ) used to access the Site, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier. Site Usage Information collected may be non-identifying or may be associated with you. If it is associated with you, it will be treated as Personal Information. The methods that may be used to collect Site Usage Information include the following:

**Cookies.** A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Site. A Flash Cookie is a data file placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plugin that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device. Cookies and Flash Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, to remember you and your preferences and web pages visited while using the Site. You may disable cookies or Flash Cookies on your Device, but some features of the Site may not function properly.

**Web Beacons.** Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as "1x1 GIFs" or "clear GIFs") may be included in our web pages and email messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or email can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Site, to monitor how users navigate the Site, to count how many emails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

**Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our Web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

#### 2\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We may share non-personally identifiable information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third-parties. We do not provide your Personal Information to third-parties for those third-parties’ marketing purposes unless you consent to such sharing at the time you provide your Personal Information. We may use your Personal Information for promotional and marketing purposes with companies with whom we enter into marketing and promotional arrangements.

We may also share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described in this Privacy Policy and in the following circumstances: 

**(a) When You Post Information to a Third-Party Web Site or Interact with Third-Party Widgets**   
The Site may allow you to share certain information with third-party web sites by posting to your account on those third-party sites. For example, you could choose to share with your Facebook profile information about your activity on the Site. Also, your interactions with third-party widgets on the Site may send information to that third-party if you have an account with that third-party. For example, a third-party widget on the Site may allow you to rate a book on the Site and, if you have an account with the third-party owner of the widget, your rating choice will be transferred to that third-party. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of these third-parties and web sites and, therefore, you should review their privacy policies and practices prior to agreeing to share your information.

**(b) When You Agree To Receive Information From Third-Parties**   
You may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers from one or more third-parties. **If you agree at that time to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to that third-party (or parties) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of that third-party.** We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third-parties and, therefore, you should review the privacy policies and practices of third-parties prior to agreeing to share your information. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communication from a third-party, you will need to contact that third-party directly.

**(c) Third-Parties Providing Services on our Behalf**   
We may use third-party vendors to perform certain services on behalf of the Site, such as hosting the Site, designing and/or operating the Site's features, tracking Site analytics, enabling BOOKISH to send you email, or performing other administrative services. We may provide these companies with access to user information, including Personal Information, to carry out the services they are performing for you or for BOOKISH. We may share your Personal Information with our third-party vendors that provide internal support to BOOKISH's and the Site's operations including maintenance, management, storage, disposal of Personal Information and/or fulfillment of various sweepstakes, rebate offers and services.

**(d) Contests and Promotions**   
We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a **"Promotion"** ) through the Site that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the terms, conditions or official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third-parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules such as on a winners list.

**(e) Administrative and Legal Reasons**   
We may transfer and disclose user information, including Personal Information, to third-parties: (i) in the event we are required to respond to subpoenas or other legal process or if in our good faith opinion such disclosure is required by law; (ii) at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; or (iii) to protect and/or defend the Site's [Terms of Use](http://bookish.com/terms-of-use) or other policies applicable to the Site or to protect the personal safety, rights, property or security of BOOKISH or any individual. We may also use Device Identifiers, including IP addresses, to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, Internet service providers, wireless service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

**(f) Business Transfers**   
We may share your Personal Information with our corporate parents and other entities affiliated with us for business and operational purposes. BOOKISH also reserves the right to disclose and transfer all information related to the Site, including Personal Information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Site or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of BOOKISH's stock and/or assets or other corporate change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.

#### 3\. YOUR CHOICES

As noted in this Privacy Policy, we may contact you to provide you with information about programs and services that may be of interest to you. You can "opt-out" of receiving advertising and promotional email from us by following the opt-out instructions in our email messages. To ensure that your opt-out request is honored, you must use the designated method in the email message to notify us of your opt-out request, as we cannot guarantee that other methods of notification will be effective or timely. Please note that even if you chose to opt-out of our emails, we will continue to send you important service related communications, including follow-up messages regarding sweepstakes or contests you have entered, as applicable, or other transactions you have undertaken (e.g., order confirmation).You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration. 

The Site may allow you to correct or update Personal Information you have provided through a form on the Site or otherwise. If you wish to close your Profile on the Site, you can email [support@bookish.com](mailto:support@bookish.com) and request that your Profile be closed. BOOKISH will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. When you edit your Personal Information or change your preferences on the Site, this information may persist internally for BOOKISH's administrative purposes. If you wish to close your Profile or request, please note that it may not be feasible for us to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons, and if you have made any public postings on the Site, such as in the Public Areas, these communications may remain publically available. If you have registered for BOOKISH through a third-party account, such as Facebook or Twitter, and you delete or remove that third-party account, you may not be able to access your Bookish account.

#### 4\. THIRD-PARTY CONTENT, LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES, AND WIDGETS

The Site may contain content that is supplied by a third-party, including advertisers, and those third-parties may collect Site Usage Information and your Device Identifier when web pages from the Site are served to your Device. In addition, the Site may contain links to third-party web sites that BOOKISH does not control. For example, if you "click" on a link from an advertisement or sponsorship link on BOOKISH, the "click" may take you off the Site and onto a different web site. These links could include links from sponsors, advertisers and others that may reference the Site or the Site's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. Also, Site widgets may be included on third-party web pages and web sites that are not associated with BOOKISH and over which we have no control. BOOKISH is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by any third-party web site. These other web sites may set cookies on your Device, independently collect data or solicit Personal Information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. BOOKISH encourages you to be aware of when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of all third-party web sites before submitting any Personal Information to those sites.

#### 5\. ONLINE SHOPPING

Note that when you click a link to buy a book or other material or services on the Site, you may be forwarded to a different site for the transaction ( **"Transaction Site"** ). The personal and payment information you submit on the Transaction Site is subject to the [Privacy Policy](http://bookish.com/), [Terms of Use](http://bookish.com/terms-of-use) and any other relevant policies on the Transaction Site. Please review those documents to ensure that you agree with them before placing an order on the Transaction Site. We may use your Personal Information, (but not your credit card number) to contact you about future products, services and discounts.

#### 6\. SECURITY

Please remember that no data transmission over the Internet, or by other means, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Therefore, you understand, acknowledge, and agree that you transmit certain Personal Information over this Site, any Transaction Site and any linked or affiliated sites at your own risk. Once we receive your data, we shall use commercially reasonable efforts to help protect and secure the information you provide to us.

#### 7\. CHILDREN

The Site is a general audience web site and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children younger than age 13. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not provide any Personal Information to us. If we are notified that a person under 13 years of age has submitted Personal Information to us, we will close that person’s account or take other appropriate action.

#### 8\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

BOOKISH reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy. BOOKISH will not, however, use your Personal Information without your consent in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time it was collected.

#### 9\. CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy or our practices, you may contact us by email to the attention of the Privacy Administrator at [support@bookish.com](mailto:support@bookish.com).

### Exquiro, Inc. Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 4, 2013 ("Effective Date").

The Privacy Policy applies to personal information that may be collected when a user or customer (hereinafter “User”, “you”, “your”, and “yours”) interacts (a) with Exquiro, Inc., and its parents, subsidiaries, or affiliates (hereinafter "Retailer”, “we”, “our”, and “ours”), (b) Retailer’s websites and applications, or (c) online retail stores operated by Retailer.

**By doing business with or interacting with Retailer in the manner described in this Privacy Policy at any time on or after the Effective Date, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the application of this Privacy Policy to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of all your personal information as described. If you choose to visit a Retailer website or online retail store, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Notice and Retailer’s Terms of Use, available at http://www.bookish.com/privacy-policy, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the State of New York.**

**Retailer reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time.**

**1\. Types of Personal Information that Retailer Collects**

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. For example, personal information can include your name in combination with your e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, phone number, or credit card information.

**2\. Purposes for Collecting Personal Data**

We collect your personal information in an effort to enhance your customer experience and, as necessary, to administer our business. It allows us to provide you with better access to our products and services, with a particular focus on the items and programs that may be of most interest to you. For more information as to why we collect personal information, please see the section below entitled: "How Retailer Uses Personal Information".

Your personal information also allows us to communicate with you about special offers, promotions, and other marketing programs and news that may be of interest to you.

**3\. How Retailer Collects Personal Information**

**(a). Information that you provide to us**

As a general matter, you can browse in our stores and on our websites without submitting your personal information to us. However, there are a number of circumstances in which you may need to provide us with your personal information. The most common of these circumstances include: • Making a purchase or placing an order

• Creating an online account

• Submitting a customer review, a list, or other user-created content or participating in book clubs

• Posting a blog, or participating in other Retailer facilitated online interactive services

• Contacting customer service

For your convenience, we have provided a summary description of each of these circumstances below.

**Making a purchase or placing an order**

When you make a purchase or place an order in our stores or place an order online without an account, you may need to submit personal information to us.

**Creating an online account**

You can create a password-protected account to complete your online order, to purchase or download eBooks, digital magazines, digital newspapers, digital journals and other periodicals, blogs, other digital content ("Digital Content") or the e-Reader software, to save items to an electronic shopping cart, or to join a Retailer facilitated online interactive service. To create any of these accounts, we will ask you to provide us with personal information. If you use your online account to make a purchase or download, we will use the personal information stored in your account and/or require you to input additional personal information, such as credit card information, to complete your order or download.

**Submitting a customer review, list, blog posting, or other user-created content, participating in a book club, or participating in some other Retailer facilitated online interactive service**

You may choose to submit an online customer review, list, blog posting, or other user-created content, participate in online book clubs, or participate in some other Retailer facilitated online interactive service. Because any information you choose to post will be available on the Internet, we can make no assurances that others will not use, or misuse, that information.

**Contacting Customer Service**

When you contact customer service, we may ask you to provide, or confirm, personal information so that we can better serve you.

**(b) Information automatically collected**

There are circumstances in which we automatically receive and collect information from you. The most common sources of this information include: • Cookies

• Pixel tags or GIFs

• Business partners, contractors, shared databases, and other third parties

For your convenience, we have provided a summary description of each of these circumstances below.

**Information automatically collected when you visit our websites**

When you visit our websites or online retail stores, we automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. For example, we may receive and collect: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to monitor the usage of our websites and online retail stores and as necessary for our business. This information does not include personal information.

**Information collected using cookies**

Like many online retailers, we use cookies to personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience. Cookies are small files that we place on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on our websites. Cookies help us to: (1) speed navigation, keep track of items in your shopping bag and provide you with content that is tailored to you; (2) remember information you gave us so that you don't have to reenter it; (3) determine the effectiveness of some of our marketing efforts and communications; and (4) monitor the total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of banners displayed.

Browsers are typically set to create cookies automatically. You can choose to have your browser notify you when cookies are being written to your computer or accessed, or you can disable cookies entirely. If you disable cookies, however, you will not be able to place items in an online shopping cart, and therefore you will not be able to place an order with us online. Also, by not using cookies, some Retailer website features and services may not function properly.

**Information regarding emails sent to you collected using pixel tags or clear GIFs**

To help us understand the effectiveness of certain of our communications and marketing efforts, we may use "message format" and "message open" sensing technologies that use pixel tags or clear GIFs (which are also called web beacons). These technologies allow us to know if your e-mail program is able to accept HTML e-mails and, if it is, to: (1) send you e-mails in that format; and (2) determine if you have opened our e-mail messages.

**Information collected from outside sources**

We may periodically collect personal information and other information about you from business partners, contractors and other third parties. This includes, but is not limited to, instances in which you affirmatively authorize third parties to provide us with information.

**Information collected from visitors from outside the United States**

If you are visiting Retailer’s websites or online retail stores from outside the United States and provide us with personal information, please note that your personal information will be transferred, stored and processed within the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. **By doing business or interacting with Retailer, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to facilities located in the United States and other facility locations selected by Retailer.**

**4\. How Retailer Uses Personal Information**

Retailer uses your personal information to provide you with an enhanced customer experience on and through our websites and online retail stores, as necessary, to administer our business. For example, we use your personal information to: • Provide you with products and services and information and display associated content and advertising;

• Provide customer service;

• Conduct research and perform analysis in order to measure, maintain, protect, develop and improve our products and services;

• Administer sweepstakes, contests, promotions or surveys;

• Communicate with you about special offers, events, or new products or services that may be of interest to you;

• Customize and enhance our websites and advertising;

• Make communications necessary to notify you regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues; and

• Manage our business.

**5\. Parties With Whom Retailer Shares Personal Information**

**Retailer DOES NOT SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES.**

Retailer shares your personal information with:

**Other entities owned by Retailer.** Some of our customers purchase items from us on more than one website or online retail stores. We share your personal information within the Retailer enterprise to improve your shopping or browsing experience at multiple Retailer operated websites and online retail stores.

**Service providers, subcontractors and agents who perform services on our behalf.** We provide personal information to third party service providers, subcontractors, and agents that work under contract on our behalf to provide certain services. These third parties do not have the right to use personal information we provide to them in any way that is not authorized by Retailer. They are contractually obligated to use such information only as necessary to assist us and to maintain the confidentiality and security of such information.

**Third party providers of products and services.** These are third parties that provide products and services you may purchase or request from or through Retailer (e.g., parties performing order fulfillment and content providers). These third parties do not have the right to use personal information we provide to them in any way that is not authorized by Retailer.

In connection with some magazine or newspaper subscriptions and single issue purchases of magazines or newspapers placed on Retailer’s websites and online retail stores, in order to complete your transaction, we may need to forward your name, magazine or newspaper order, email address, and shipping or billing address to our content providers. The content providers will share your magazine or newspaper order information as well as your name and address, or name and e-mail and shipping or billing addresses with the magazine or newspaper publisher and magazine or newspaper circulation auditors. Magazine and newspaper publishers may use this information to fulfill your order and for other purposes. Your credit card information will not be shared with them.

In connection with purchases of certain digital content through websites and online retail stores operated by Retailer, we may need to forward information about you (including, for example, your Internet Protocol (IP) address) to the digital content provider in order to enable you to download or purchase digital content from or through that provider. In each such instance, the digital content provider is obligated to use such information in accordance with its own privacy policy and applicable law.

**Credit Card Companies.** Credit card transactions are handled by third party financial institutions and their vendors and contractors who receive credit card numbers and other personal information from us to verify the credit card numbers and process transactions.

**Law enforcement officials and as required by law.** Retailer may release personal information to third parties when we determine, in our judgment, that it is necessary to (a) comply with the law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce or apply the terms of any of our policies or user agreements; or (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Retailer, our employees, our customers, users, or others.

**Co-branded offerings.** In some instances, we may offer a service or feature that is co-branded by Retailer and a third party. If you provide information in connection with such co-branded service or feature, that information may be shared between Retailer and the third party. Although Retailer's treatment of the information is governed by this policy, the third party's treatment of your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy.

**Other websites operated by Retailer.** In some instances, we may operate a website on behalf of a third party (e.g., a university’s online bookstore). If you provide information in connection with a third party website operated by Retailer, that information may be shared between Retailer and the third party. Although Retailer’s treatment of the information is governed by this policy, the third party's treatment of your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy.

**Retail services operated by Retailer on Third Party Websites.** In some instances, we may operate on behalf of a third party a "shopping cart" or online location in which a user may purchase or place orders (e.g., Bookish LLC). If you provide information to Retailer in connection with a third party website, that information may be shared between Retailer and the third party. Although Retailer’s treatment of the information is governed by this policy, the third party's treatment of your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy.

**Sales, Mergers, and Acquisitions.** If Retailer becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, personal information may be provided to the entities and advisors involved subject to a confidentiality agreement, and we will provide notice before any personal information is finally transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**6\. How Retailer Secures Personal Information**

We take significant and appropriate security measures, including physical, technological and procedural measures, to help to safeguard your personal information and to prevent unauthorized access and disclosure. In addition, we use industry-standard technology, such as firewalls and encryption in the transmission of certain sensitive personal information, designed to prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information, and, as technology develops, we intend to take additional measures to improve security. While we are focused on the security of your personal information and follow strict standards, processes and procedures that are designed to protect your personal information, we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will remain secure in all circumstances.

**7\. How You can Manage Retailer’s Promotional Communications Directed to You**

When you interact with Retailer in certain ways, you may be eligible to receive certain marketing-related and promotional communications as well as special offers (collectively "Promotional Communications") from Retailer that may include advertisements from third parties. The most common of these circumstances include:

• Making a purchase or download or placing an order

• Creating an online account

• Joining an online interactive service

• Signing up with websites and online retail stores operated by Retailer

• Entering a sweepstakes or a contest

If, at any time, you wish to no longer receive Promotional Communications from Retailer, please contact the Retailer customer service [customerservice@exquirofulfillment.com](mailto:customerservice@exquirofulfillment.com)

Even if you opt-out of receiving Promotional Communications, you may continue to receive e-mails relating to order confirmations, back order notifications, membership information, and/or other business-related communications. Although the primary purpose of these emails is not to provide you with promotional material, they may contain within them some promotional material.

_Note for Interactive Service Users_

By participating in an online interactive service facilitated by Retailer, and using Retailer's various interactive offerings, including the submission of customer reviews, you agree to receive communications from Retailer, other users, and moderators related to the provision of these services.

**8\. Whom You may Contact if You Have Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at customerservice@exquirofulfillment.com .

**9\. Retailer’s Privacy Policy Regarding Children**

Our products and services are marketed for and directed towards purchase by adults or with the consent of adults. Individuals under the age of 18 ("Minors") are not permitted to use Retailer websites and online retail stores without the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. Furthermore, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for an online account or to post personal information on our websites. Should we learn that someone under the age of 13 has provided any personal information to or on any of the Retailer websites or online retail stores, we will remove that information as soon as possible.
